BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 8) 6178/008
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series IX: Industry Code #44, Retail Trade
  - Code no.6300: Food Employers Council and IBT, 1970-1991 (Box 176, Folder 6)
    - Item 4: Food Employers Council, Inc. & Unaffiliated Grocery Companies and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 87, 467, 542, 631, 692, 848, 871 and 952, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 9/3/1979 and expires on 9/5/1982. Covers 1400 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 5: Food Employers Council, Inc. & Unaffiliated Grocery Companies and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 87, 467, 542, 572, 631, 692, 848 and 952, 1982-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 9/6/1982 and expires on 9/8/1985. Covers 1500 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 6: Food Employers Council, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 63, 87, 542, 572, 630, 631, 848 and 952, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 6)
      Agreement effective 12/30/1985 and expires on 9/11/1988. Covers an unknown number of workers in Southern CA
  - Code no.6302: Food Employers Council and IBT, 1970-1991 (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Item 1: Food Employers Council, Inc. & Unaffiliated Grocery Companies and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 235, 467, 542, 595 and 871, 1970-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 9/7/1970 and expires on 9/2/1973. Covers 3000 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 2: Food Employers Council, Inc. & Unaffiliated Grocery Companies and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 87, 235, 467, 542, 595, 692 and 871, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 9/3/1973 and expires on 9/5/1976. Covers 3250 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 3: Food Employers Council, Inc. & Unaffiliated Grocery Companies and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 87, 235, 467, 542, 595, 692 and 871 Memorandum, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Item 4: Food Employers Council, Inc. & Unaffiliated Grocery Companies and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 235, 467, 542, 595, 692 and 871, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 9/6/1976 and expires on 9/2/1979. Covers 3500 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 5: Food Employers Council, Inc. & Unaffiliated Grocery Companies and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 467, 542, 572, 595, 692, 871 and 952, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 9/3/1979 and expires on 9/5/1982. Covers 4060 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 6: Food Employers Council, Inc. & Unaffiliated Grocery Companies and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 467, 542, 572, 595, 692 and 952, 1982-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 9/6/1982 and expires on 9/8/1985. Covers 4000 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 7: Food Employers Council, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 63, 542, 572, 630 and 952, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 7)
    - Item 8: Food Employers Council, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 63, 542, 630 and 952, 1988-1991; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 7)
      Agreement effective 9/12/1988 and expires on 9/8/1991. Covers an unknown number of workers in Southern CA
  - Code no.6316: Food Employers Council and Service Employees International Union, 1973-1991 (Box 176, Folder 8)
    - Item 1: Retail food stores and Service and Hospital Employees Union, AFL- CIO, Local 399, 1973-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1973 and expires on 12/30/1975. Covers an unknown number of workers in Southern CA
    - Item 2: Retail food stores and Hospital and Service Employees Union, AFL- CIO, Local 399, 1975-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 10/20/1975 and expires on 12/31/1978. Covers 1000 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 3: Retail food stores and Hospital and Service Employees Union, AFL- CIO, Local 399, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1979 and expires on 1/3/1982. Covers 1140 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 4: Retail food stores and Hospital and Service Employees Union, AFL- CIO, Local 399, 1982-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 1/4/1982 and expires on 1/6/1985. Covers 1500 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 5: Food Employers Council, Inc. and Hospital and Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 399, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 7/1/1985 and expires on 1/10/1988. Covers an unknown number of workers in Southern CA
    - Item 6: Food Employers Council, Inc. and Hospital and Service Employees Union, AFL-CIO, Local 399, 1988-1991; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 8)
      Agreement effective 1/11/1988 and expires on 1/13/1991. Covers an unknown number of workers in Southern CA
  - Code no.6333: Food Employers Council and IBT, 1973-1991 (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Item 1: Food Employers Council, Inc. & Unaffiliated Grocery Companies and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 235, 467, 542, 572 and 595, 1973-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 9/3/1973 and expires on 9/5/1976. Covers 1300 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 2: Food Employers Council, Inc. & Unaffiliated Grocery Companies and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 235, 467, 542, 572 and 595, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 9/6/1976 and expires on 9/2/1979. Covers 1400 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 3: Food Employers Council, Inc. & Unaffiliated Grocery Companies and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 467, 542, 572, 595 and 952, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 9/3/1979 and expires on 9/5/1982. Covers 1550 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 4: Food Employers Council, Inc. & Unaffiliated Grocery Companies and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 467, 542, 572, 595 and 952, 1982-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 9)
      Agreement effective 9/6/1982 and expires on 9/8/1985. Covers 1400 workers in Southern CA
    - Item 5: Food Employers Council, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 63, 572, 630 and 952, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 9)
    - Item 6: Food Employers Council, Inc. and International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Locals 63, 572, 630 and 952, 1988-1991; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - Code no.6338: Food Fair Inc. (Division of Bruno's Inc.) and UFCW, 1990-2003 (Box 176, Folder 10)
    1990-1998, 1999- 2003
    - Item 1: Food Fair and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1657, 1990-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 8/26/1990 and expires on 2/26/1994. Covers an unknown number of workers in Alabama
    - Item 2: Food Fair and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1657, 1994-1998; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 2/27/1994 and expires on 2/28/1998. Covers an unknown number of workers in Alabama
    - Item 3: Bruno's Inc., d/b/a Food Fair and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1657, 1999-2003; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 10)
      Agreement effective 9/26/1999 and expires on 9/27/2003. Covers an unknown number of workers in Alabama
  - Code no.6701: Acme Markets and UFCW, 1961-1984 (Box 176, Folder 11)
    - Item 1: American Stores Company, Zone No. 7 and Retail Food Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1245, 1961-1963; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 3/4/1961 and expires on 8/30/1963. Covers 3000 workers in New Jersey
    - Item 2: Acme Markets, Inc., Division #7 and Retail Food Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1245, 1963-1966; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 8/31/1963 and expires on 9/2/1966. Covers an unknown number of workers in New Jersey
    - Item 3: Acme Markets, Inc., Division #7 and Retail Food Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1245, 1966-1969; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 9/3/1966 and expires on 9/26/1969. Covers 1400 workers in New Jersey
    - Item 4: Acme Markets, Inc., Division #7 and Retail Food Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1245, 1969-1972; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 9/27/1969 and expires on 9/29/1972. Covers 2215 workers in New Jersey
    - Item 5: Acme Markets, Inc., Division #7 and Retail Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1245, 1972-1973; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 9/30/1972 and expires on 9/28/1973. Covers 1800 workers in New Jersey
    - Item 6: Acme Markets and Retail Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1245 Memorandum, 1973-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 9/29/1973 and expires on 9/28/1975. Covers 2000 workers in New Jersey
    - Item 7: Acme Markets, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1245 Memorandum, 1975-1978; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 10/4/1975 and expires on 10/6/1978. Covers 2108 workers in New Jersey
    - Item 8: Acme Markets, Inc., Division #7 and Retail Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1245, 1978-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 10/8/1978 and expires on 10/10/1981. Covers 1700 workers in New Jersey
    - Item 9: Acme Markets, Inc., Region East and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1245, 1981-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 11)
      Agreement effective 10/11/1981 and expires on 10/13/1984. Covers 2300 workers in New Jersey
  - Code no.6704: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and UFCW, 1974-1987 (Box 176, Folder 12)
    - Item 1: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Retail Store Employees Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 880, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1974 and expires on 9/4/1977. Covers 800 workers in Ohio
    - Item 2: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Retail Store Employees Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 880, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 9/4/1977 and expires on 8/31/1980. Covers an unknown number of workers in Ohio
    - Item 3: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and Retail Store Employees Union, United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 880, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 9/1/1980 and expires on 9/4/1983. Covers an unknown number of workers in Ohio
    - Item 4: Cleveland Food Industry Committee and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 880, 1984-1987; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 12)
      Agreement effective 9/11/1984 and expires on 9/13/1987. Covers 7350 workers in Ohio
  - Code no.6706: First National Supermarkets and UFCW, 1974-1991 (Box 176, Folder 13)
    - Item 1: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 371, 1974-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 3/4/1974 and expires on 4/3/1976. Covers 2897 workers in Connecticut; Massachusetts
    - Item 2: First National Stores, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 371, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 4/4/1976 and expires on 3/4/1979. Covers 2469 workers in Connecticut; Massachusetts
    - Item 3: First National Supermarkets, Inc. and Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 371, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 3/5/1979 and expires on 3/7/1982. Covers 2718 workers in Connecticut; Massachusetts
    - Item 4: First National Supermarkets, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 371, 1982-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 3/7/1982 and expires on 5/5/1985. Covers 3000 workers in Connecticut; Massachusetts
    - Item 5: First National Supermarkets, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 371, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 5/5/1985 and expires on 5/8/1988. Covers 4300 workers in Connecticut; Massachusetts
    - Item 6: First National Supermarkets, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 371, 1988-1991; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 13)
      Agreement effective 5/9/1988 and expires on 5/5/1991. Covers 4400 workers in Connecticut; Massachusetts
  - Code no.6715: Allied Employers, Inc. and UFCW, 1971-1989 (Box 176, Folder 14)
    - Item 1: Allied Employers, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1105, 1971-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1971 and expires on 4/1/1975. Covers 3800 workers in King Co., WA; Snohomish Co., WA
    - Item 2: Allied Employers, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1105, 1971-1975; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1971 and expires on 4/1/1975. Covers an unknown number of workers in King Co., WA; Snohomish Co., WA
    - Item 3: Allied Employers, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1105, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1974 and expires on 4/1/1977. Covers an unknown number of workers in King Co., WA; Snohomish Co., WA
    - Item 4: Allied Employers, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1105, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1977 and expires on 4/1/1980. Covers 4000 workers in King Co., WA; Snohomish Co., WA
    - Item 5: Allied Employers, Inc. and Retail Clerks Union, United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1105, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 4/1/1980 and expires on 4/3/1983. Covers 5000 workers in King Co., WA; Snohomish Co., WA
    - Item 6: Allied Employers, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1105, 1983-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 4/3/1983 and expires on 5/4/1986. Covers 6800 workers in King Co., WA; Snohomish Co., WA
    - Item 7: Allied Employers, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1105, 1986-1989; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 14)
      Agreement effective 5/4/1986 and expires on 5/7/1989. Covers 8000 workers in King Co., WA; Snohomish Co., WA
  - Code no.6725: Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Co. and UFCW, 1993-1996 (Box 176, Folder 15)
    - Item 1: The Great Atlantic and Pacific Tea Company, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 464A, 1993-1996; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 15)
      Agreement effective 4/25/1993 and expires on 7/27/1996. Covers 5000 workers in New Jersey
  - Code no.6730: Food Employers Inc. and UFCW, 1978-1994 (Box 176, Folder 16)
    - Item 1: Food Employers, Inc. and Retail Employees Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 1092, 1978-1981; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 6/4/1978 and expires on 6/6/1981. Covers 4175 workers in Oregon
    - Item 2: Food Employers, Inc. and Retail Employees Union, United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 1092, 1981-1984; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 6/7/1981 and expires on 7/7/1984. Covers 4200 workers in Oregon
    - Item 3: Food Employers, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 555, 1987-1990; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 7/12/1987 and expires on 7/14/1990. Covers an unknown number of workers in Oregon
    - Item 4: Food Employers, Inc. and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 555, 1990-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 16)
      Agreement effective 1/1/1990 and expires on 7/16/1994. Covers an unknown number of workers in Oregon
  - Code no.6733: Chain Grocery Stores and UFCW, 1994-1994 (Box 176, Folder 17)
    - Item 1: Retail food stores and Retail Store Employees Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 655, 1994-1976; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 5/5/1994 and expires on 5/5/1976. Covers 7500 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 2: Retail food stores and Retail Store Employees Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 655, 1976-1979; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 5/5/1976 and expires on 5/5/1979. Covers 7500 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 3: Retail food stores and Retail Store Employees Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 655, 1979-1982; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 5/6/1979 and expires on 5/8/1982. Covers 8500 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 4: Retail food stores and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL- CIO, Local 655, 1982-1985; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 5/9/1982 and expires on 5/11/1985. Covers 8500 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 5: Retail food stores and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL- CIO, Local 655, 1985-1988; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 5/12/1985 and expires on 6/18/1988. Covers 7000 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 6: Retail food stores and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL- CIO, Local 655, 1988-1991; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 6/19/1988 and expires on 6/15/1991. Covers 10000 workers in St. Louis, MO
    - Item 7: Retail food stores and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL- CIO, Local 655, 1991-1994; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 17)
      Agreement effective 6/16/1991 and expires on 6/11/1994. Covers 10400 workers in St. Louis, MO
  - Code no.6736: Master Food and Liquor Agreement and UFCW, 1971-1986 (Box 176, Folder 18)
    - Item 1: Food and liquor employers and Retail Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 588, 1971-1974; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1971 and expires on 5/31/1974. Covers 3500 workers in Sacramento Co., CA; Yolo Co., CA; Placer Co., CA; El Dorado Co., CA; Amador Co., CA; Calaveras Co., CA; Tuolumne Co., CA; Stanislaus Co., CA
    - Item 2: Food and liquor employers and Retail Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 588, 1974-1977; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 6/1/1974 and expires on 2/26/1977. Covers 4488 workers in Sacramento Co., CA; Yolo Co., CA; Placer Co., CA; El Dorado Co., CA; Amador Co., CA; Calaveras Co., CA; Tuolumne Co., CA; Stanislaus Co., CA
    - Item 3: Food and liquor employers and Retail Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 588, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 2/27/1977 and expires on 2/29/1980. Covers 4068 workers in Sacramento Co., CA; Yolo Co., CA; Placer Co., CA; El Dorado Co., CA; Amador Co., CA; Calaveras Co., CA; Tuolumne Co., CA; Stanislaus Co., CA
    - Item 4: Food and liquor employers and Retail Clerks Union, Retail Clerks International Association, AFL-CIO, Local 588 Errata, 1977-1980; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 2/27/1977 and expires on 2/29/1980. Covers an unknown number of workers in Sacramento Co., CA; Yolo Co., CA; Placer Co., CA; El Dorado Co., CA; Amador Co., CA; Calaveras Co., CA; Tuolumne Co., CA; Stanislaus Co., CA
    - Item 5: Food and liquor employers and Retail Clerks Union, United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 588, 1980-1983; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1980 and expires on 2/28/1983. Covers 4600 workers in Sacramento Co., CA; Yolo Co., CA; Placer Co., CA; El Dorado Co., CA; Amador Co., CA; Calaveras Co., CA; Tuolumne Co., CA; Stanislaus Co., CA
    - Item 6: Food and Liquor Employers and United Food and Commercial Workers, AFL-CIO, Local 588, 1983-1986; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 18)
      Agreement effective 3/1/1983 and expires on 2/26/1986. Covers an unknown number of workers in Sacramento Co., CA; Yolo Co., CA; Placer Co., CA; El Dorado Co., CA; Amador Co., CA; Calaveras Co., CA; Tuolumne Co., CA; Stanislaus Co., CA; San Joaquin Co., CA
  - Code no.6743: Food Employers Council Inc. and UFCW, 1964-1995 (Box 176, Folder 19)
    - Item 1: Retail Meat Markets and Butchers' Union, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 115, 1964-1967; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 19)
      Agreement effective 10/1/1964 and expires on 10/1/1967. Covers an unknown number of workers in Northern CA
    - Item 2: Retail Meat Markets and Butchers' Union, Amalgamated Meat Cutters and Butcher Workmen of North America, AFL-CIO, Local 115, 1967-1970; Collective Bargaining Agreement (CBA) (Box 176, Folder 19)